Guide to the Society for the Psychological Study of Lesbian and Gay Issues records, 1981-2006
Society for the Psychological Study of Lesbian and Gay Issues records, 1981-2006
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Society for the Psychological Study of Lesbian and Gay Issues records, 1981-2006
7580
Society for the Psychological Study of Lesbian and Gay Issues
9.4 cubic ft.; 13 videos
Announcements, petitions, minutes, audiotapes, photographs, correspondence, bylaws, financial records, reports, videotapes.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Announcements and petitions for the creation of a new division within the American Psychological Association, Division 44; the Division's minutes, audiotapes of meetings, photographs, correspondence, bylaws, financial records, and reports. Revisions to the APA's Diagnostic and Statistical Manual (DSM) are a major area of focus. Includes videos of APA's first Symposium, interviews with Evelyn Hooker, Del Martin, and others, and the 1989 meetings.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
From 1981-1984, members of the American Psychological Association and an independent organization, the Association of Lesbian and Gay Psychologists, petitioned APA to create a new division focusing on lesbian and gay issues. Division 44 of APA, the Society for the Psychological Study of Lesbian and Gay Issues, was founded in 1985. Its members are mostly academic and applied psychologists and most are members of APA.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Announcements and petitions for the creation of a new division within the American Psychological Association; the minutes of the Division's Executive Committee and other committees, audio tapes of meetings, photographs, correspondence, bylaws, financial records, and reports. Revisions to the APA's Diagnostic and Statistical Manual (DSM) are a major area of focus. Includes 1984-2000 files from Doug Kimmel, who served as program chair from 1985-1986 and president from 1986-1987. Includes videos of APA's first Symposium and interviews with Evelyn Hooker, Del Martin, and others from 1985-1990.
Treasurer's files, 1997-2001, from Michael R. Stevenson; Executive Committee reports and meeting minutes, 2001-2005, including Transgender Task Force Mission Statement and meeting minutes; and 2002 Executive Committee and business meeting files from Allen M. Omoto.
Also a 1994 amicus brief in a Cincinnati case; and Susan Cochran's files from the Task force on Treatment Guidelines, 1984-1988, during much of which time Alan Maylon and Kristin Hancock were co-chairs.
Files from Division 44 President Judith M. Glassgold, 2002-2005, including 1999 and 2001 APA Governance Survey results, correspondence about APA's policy on job advertisements, a 2004 briefing book by the APA Task Force on Sexual Orientation and Military Service, a 2002 letter about conversion therapy, the 2000 membership diractory, and 2001 correspondence about APA's proposal to eliminate "Footnote 4" from its accreditation standards for psychology programs. Footnote 4 allows religious institutions exemptions from following APA's diversity standards. Also, membership survey information, 1999-2006.
Files from Armand Cerbone, co-chair of the Joint Task Force to write guidelines for Psychotherapy with LGB clients 1990-2000, including correspondence and drafts pertaining to the writing of the guidelines (adopted by the APA February 26, 2000); news articles and correspondence regarding the debate in the Council of Representatives over the APA's ban on military advertising; and correspondence and planning documents for a Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Concerns International Conference held in 2001.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Society for the Psychological Study of Lesbian and Gay Issues.; American Psychological Association. Division 44.; Cerbone, Armand R.; Cochran, Susan.; Hancock, Kristin.; Hooker, Evelyn Caldwell.; Kimmel, Doug.; Martin, Del.; Maylon, Alan.
Subjects:
Psychology--Study and teaching.; Gays.; Gender identity.; Lesbians.; Psychologists--Societies, etc.; Sex (Psychology).; Sexual orientation.; Sex differences (Psychology).; Sex role.; Transsexuals.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
RELATED MATERIAL
Related Collection: Association of Gay and Lesbian Psychologists records, #7592.
Related Publication: Division 44 Newsletter, Human Sexuality HQ75 .D61
SERIES LIST
Series I. Correspondence
Boxes 1, 3, 5, 7-8
Series II. Internal Files
Boxes 1-11
Administration (membership, newsletter, publicity)
Meeting Materials (agendas, minutes, notes, presentations, reports)
Budget
Individual Professional Papers (Jeffrey Rehm)
Committees and Associations
Task Force on Future Directions
Association of Gay Psychologists (AGP)
Board of Professional Affairs (BPA)
Committee on Gay and Lesbian Issues
Committee on Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual and Transgender Concerns
American Psychological Association (APA)
Task Force on Diagnostic Concerns
Joint Council on Professional Education in Psychology (JCPEP)
Committee on Lesbian and Gay Family Issues (CLGFI)
Task Force on Treatment Guidelines
Council of Representatives (COR)
Lesbian, Gay, and Bisexual Concerns International Conference (LBGCIC)
Joint Task Force (JTF) to write Guidelines for Psychotherapy with Gay, Lesbian, and Bisexual Clients
Accreditation
Annual Committee
Bisexuality Task Force
Continuing Education Committee
Fellows Committee
Ethnic Minority Affairs Committee
Science Task Force
Student Representatives
Youth and Family Task Force
Series III. Audiotapes
Box 4-5
Series IV. Photographs
Box 3, 6
Series V. Subject Files
Boxes 3, 4
Series VI. Miscellaneous
Boxes 3-6, 8, 11
General
Correspondence
Members
Series VII. Videotapes
Boxes 3, 4
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Correspondence
  - Transmittal letter, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Maylon and Penlea, Rochlin from Susan Gore in 1985/ Paper by Doug Kimmel (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Letter to Logan Wright, May 1986 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Letter to Joseph LoPiccolo, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Notes from Adrienne Smith, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - ICD-9 correspondence (International Classification of Diseases), 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - DSM-III-R correspondence (Diagnostic and Statistical Manual of Mental Disorders), 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Membership correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence from Executive Committee, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Secretary/Treasurer Correspondence, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from Executive Committee, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Secretary/Treasurer Correspondence, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence from Executive Committee, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Secretary/Treasurer Correspondence, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Unprocessed mailings from APA (American Psychological Association), 1985-86 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence re: name change to Division 44, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence re: annual [publication], 1990 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Kristin Hancock Notes and Correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Douglas Kimmel Notes and Correspondence (during presidency), 1986-1987 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - APA Division 44 Convention Program Correspondence/Information, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - APA Division 44 Convention Program Correspondence/Information, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Notes and Correspondence regarding possible establishment of Division 44 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Division 44 Secretary/Treasurer Correspondence, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Committe reports and treasurer's correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Series II. Internal Files
  - Administration (membership, newsletter, publicity)
    - Annual report, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Membership information, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Membership Committee, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Membership file, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Membership file (updated Aug. 18, 1986) (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Affiliate Dues/Second notice, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Article from Monitor, Feb. 1986 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Monitor Newsletter, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - SPSLGI (Society for Psychological Study of Lesbian and Gay Issues), 1984 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - SPSLGI minutes, correspondence, announcements, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - SPSLGI, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - SPSLGI calls, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Publicity, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - SCUM file, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Convention public information, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Symposium video project, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Letterhead masters, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Petitioner names, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Division 44 Roster, 1988-1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - APA Division 44 Newsletter Archives, 1997-1999 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - "Society for the Psychological Study of Lesbian and Gay Issues: A Division of the APA" Brochures (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Division 44 Orientation Packet, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Bylaws 1997, note 1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - New Member Surveys, Aug. 1999-Aug. 2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - New Member Surveys, July 2000-July 2001 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - New Member Surveys, Aug. 2001-July 2002 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - New Member Surveys, Aug. 2002-July 2003 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - New Member Surveys, Aug. 2003-July 2006 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Judith Glassgold (president) files, misc. (CONTAINS CD), 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Membership Directory, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Governance Surveys, 1999, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Letter to Psychotherapy ed., re: article on conversion therapy, October 16, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - "Footnote 4" correspondence, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Military issues, APA employment adverstisement policty, 1995-2001 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - APA Task Force on Sexual Orientation and Military Service Briefing Book, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - APA Requests, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Annual Report, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Annual Committee Reports, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Awards and Nominations, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Mission Statement and Bylaws, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee Address/Phone Listing, 1995-1998 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Division 44 Membership Address Listing, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - APA Convention programming, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Division 44 Retreat, January 23, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - APA Convention programming notes, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - APA Convention materials, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Liason information, August 1997 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Mailing list, April 1998 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Mission Statement (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Division 44 Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Membership: Committee Reports and Initiatives, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Newsletter, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Division 44 President Elect, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Division 44 President Elect Newsletter Statements, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Webpage Information, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Past President Survey, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - APA Convention Programming, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Division 44 Newsletters, 1986-1990 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Presidential Address and Papers, 1994-1998 (Box 11, Folder 63)
    - Procedural Documents (i.e. policies, mission statements, etc.), 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 64)
    - Division 44 Orientation Packet, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 67)
    - Annual Volume 5: Teaching LGB Psychology by Browning and Kain, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 68)
    - APA Convention, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Division 44 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Division 44 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Division 44 Post 1988 Convention to EC Meeting February 1989, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Division 44 1989 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Division 44 1990 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Meeting Materials (agendas, minutes, notes, presentations, reports)
    - Midyear meeting minutes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Previous minutes, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - NYSPA minutes (New York State Psychological Association), 1983 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee minutes, 1985-1989 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Executive Committee meeting, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Executive Committee meeting, Feb. 23, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 38-39)
    - Executive Committee meeting, Aug. 27, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Executive Committee; incoming, outgoing, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Executive Committee meeting, Mar. 29, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Midwinter meeting, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Executive Committee meeting, Aug. 23, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Executive Committee; incoming, outgoing, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Midwinter meeting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Midwinter Executive Committee meeting, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Executive Committee meeting, Aug. 1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Executive Committee; incoming, outgoing, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Midwinter Executive Committee, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Midwinter meeting, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Executive Committee; incoming, outgoing, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Midwinter Executive Committee, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Midwinter meeting, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
    - Executive Committee; incoming, outgoing, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Midwinter meeting, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Midwinter executive meeting, Los Angeles, Mar. 1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Executive Committee follow-up, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Midwinter meeting, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committee agenda meeting, Mar. 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Midwinter meeting past agendas, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Midwinter Executive Committee meeting, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 18-19)
    - Materials for Division 44 Board Meeting, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Hospitality/Planning Board Meeting, Mar. 29, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Business meeting, New Orleans, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Division 44 Midwinter Meeting, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Division 44 Convention Program - Final, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Division 44 - Convention Programming, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Division 44 - Tentative Program, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Division 44 - Program Committee, 1993-94 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Division 44 - Suite Program, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Division 44 Midwinter Meeting Materials, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Division 44 Midwinter Meeting Materials, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Division 44 Midwinter Meeting Materials, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Division 44 Midwinter Meeting, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Divion 44/APA Convention (Toronto), 1993 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Convention Meetings, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Division 44 Winter Meeting (San Diego), 1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Executive Committe meeting, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Division 44 Reports, 1997-1998 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Executive Committe meeting, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - APA/Division 44 Minutes (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Division 44 Midwinter Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 2000 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Division 44 Executive Committee Meeting, Aug. 2000 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Misc. reports, 2000-2001 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Division 44 Midwinter E.C. Meeting, Jan. 2001 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - January 2001 meeting (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Division 44 E.C. Meeting and Transgender Task Force, Aug. 2001 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - August 2001 meeting (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - 2001 meeting publications (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Division 44 Midwinter Executive Committee Meeting, Jan.-Feb. 2002 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Transgender Training, Division 44 Midwinter EC Meeting, Feb. 2002 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Executive Committee and Business Meetings, August 2002 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Division 44 Midwinter Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 2003 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Division 44 Executive Committee Meeting, Toronto, Aug. 2003 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Division 44 Executive Committee Meeting minutes, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Division 44: Executive Committee Meeting, July 2004 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Division 44: Executive Committee Meeting, Jan. 2005 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Washington, D.C. meeting, Aug. 2005 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Executive Committee Agendas, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Division 44 Minutes, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Outgoing EC Meeting, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Forging Alliances: Division 44 and 45 Joint Session, August 18, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Notes on 44 Meetings, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Incoming EC Meeting, August 26, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Mid-Winter Meeting, January 23-25, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Meeting Agendas and Annual Reports, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Division 44 and 45 Joint Session, January 1998 (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Meeting documents (retreat agenda, committee meetings), 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 65)
    - Mid-Winter Meeting and Reports, January 23-25, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 66)
    - Mid-Winter Meeting and Reports, January 28-29, 20118 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    - APA Convention Meeting and Mid-Year Reports, August 1, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 70)
    - Teleconference Minutes, 1990-04-06-1994-07-17 (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Midwinter Report, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - JTF Meeting Minutes and Documents, 1993-10-28-1994-07-17 (Box 13, Folder 66)
    - Executive Committee Minutes 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Budget
    - Task Force on Finance (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Bank statements, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Budget, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Bank statements, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Budget planning, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Expense receipts, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Revenue ledger, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Expense receipts, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Revenue ledger, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Budget, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Bank statements, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Budget, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Revenue ledger, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - APA financial information, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Expense receipts, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Tax return, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Expense receipts, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 37-38)
    - Revenues ledger, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Long distance invoices from Sprint, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Sprint statements, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Bills-paid, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Cancelled checks, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Receipts/requests for reimbursement, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Division 44 Treasury, Budgets and Vouchers, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Division 44 Tax Return, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Division 44 Bank Statements, 1990-1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Division 44 Tax Return, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Division 44 Revenue Record, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Division 44 Expense Receipts, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Division 44 Tax Return, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Division 44 Revenue Record, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Division 44 Expense Records, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Division 44 Bank Statement, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Division 44 Income Tax, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Division 44 Expense Receipts, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Division 44 Revenue Record, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Division 44 Bank Statements, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Division 44 Income, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Division 44 Expenses, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Division 44 Expenses, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Division 44 Revenue, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Alan Malyon Fund, 1992 and before (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Alan Malyon Fund, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1987-1995 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1996-1999 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Money Market, investment of funds, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Financial statements/taxes, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Financial Report, Jan-Mar 1999 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Financial Report, April-June 1999 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Financial Report, Sept-Nov 1999 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Financial Report, Oct-Nov 1999 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Income, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Expenses, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Expenses, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Financial Statements/taxes, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Financial Report, May-June 1998 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Income, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Financial Statements, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Income, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Expenses, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Financial Statements/Taxes, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Expenses, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Financial Statements/Taxes, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Expenses, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Phone cards, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1994-1996 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Budgeting, 1993-1994 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Interim Statements, 1989-1993 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Tax exempt status, 1987-1989 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Expenses, 2000; (Every 10th reimbursement request was retained by the archives) (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Financial report, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Sample Monthly Financial Report, Aug. 2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Financial Statements, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Taxes and Final Report, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Convention Receipts, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - APA Budget Updates, 1st Quarter and Aug. 2001 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Income, 2001; (1 out of 14 division receipt forms retained by the archives) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Division 44 Taxes, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Budget Requests, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Expenses, 2001; (Every 10th reimbursement request was retained by the archives) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Treasurer Report, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Mid-Year Budget Report, August 1999 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Fundraising, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Division 44 Reimbursement Forms (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Treasury Reports, 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Individual Professional Papers (Jeffrey Rehm, Douglas Kimmel)
    - Papers of Jeffrey Rehm, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
    - Papers of Jeffrey Rehm, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Papers of Jeffrey Rehm, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Documents from file of Douglas Kimmel, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Documents from file of Douglas Kimmel, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Documents from file of Douglas Kimmel, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Documents from file of Douglas Kimmel, 1988-1991 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Documents from file of Douglas Kimmel, 1992-1994 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Documents from file of Douglas Kimmel, 1994-2000 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - MATL Files- Dr. Jeffrey M. Rehm (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - MATL Files- Dr. Jeffrey M. Rehm (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Committees and Associations
    - Task Force on Future Directions
      - Task Force on Future Directions, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Task Force on Future Directions, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Task Force on Future Directions, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Association of Gay Psychologists (AGP)
      - AGP membership application (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - ALGP Presidential candidate representative, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - AGP Appreciation certificate, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 51)
      - Division 44/ALGP materials (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Division 44/ALGP materials (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - ALGP Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Division 44 and ALGP brochures and newsletters (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Board of Professional Affairs (BPA)
      - Memo from BPA meeting, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - BPA, 1995-05-21 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - COPPS, BPA, Etc. - Related Docs., 1994-01-1994-02 (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Governance Issues BPA Meeting, Review and Revisions, 1999-08-10 (Box 13, Folder 51)